A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Photo Files, RG 1 FA1128
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Individuals and Dignitaries, 1894-2002; 6
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Tribute Booklet, Undated; 9x11 booklet, with 3x5-4.5x6.5 color photos. (Box 28, Folder 394)
    Contains photos, including LSR at table with Lady Bird, and text of Liz Carpenter "Tribute to Mrs. LBJ" at Ceremonies at the Presentation of the Lady Bird Johnson Fountain, San Antonio, Texas, December 21, 1974. Undated text of (LSR?) "response to Lady Bird's toast" loosely inserted loose in booklet. Booklet created by Patsy and Marshall Steves in honor of Lady Bird's birthday.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Visits (JY Ranch), 1965-1976; Color and black and white 3x5 - 8x10 prints; 1 negative. Some snapshots stuck together. (Box 28, Folder 395)
    Lady Bird with LSR and MFR, Horace Albright, Harold Fabian, and others. Includes photo index photo no. 53 and photo no. 5238.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Visits (JY Ranch), 1970; OVERSIZED 8x10 color photo on 11x14 mat board. (Box O 63)
    With LSR and MFR at JY Ranch. Photo by Melville B. Grosvenor, National Geographic Society. Removed from frame.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Visits (Vermont), 1967 June 11; Color 8x10 photo. Print is buckled (moisture damage?). (Box 28, Folder 396)
    LSR with MFR and Lady Bird (in bonnets) in an old-fashioned car. Inscribed: "To Mary and Laurance - with happy memories of an enchanting time - and with appreciation and love, Lady Bird, June 1967." Photo by Robert L. Knudsen, The White House, stamped 11 June 1967. Removed from frame.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Visits (Woodstock, VT), 1995 October; Color 4x6 prints in 6.75 x 5.75 x 1.5 album; one loose print. (Box 28, Folder 397)
    Lady Bird Johnson visit to Woodstock mansion and Billings Farm with LSR, MFR, Nash and Bette Castro, Wes and Dee Frye, and others. Also includes 4 photos of Lady Bird and Lynda Robb at Kykuit. Album compiled by Nash Castro. Photo added to file: Lady Bird Johnson with LSR and MFR.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Visits (Williamsburg, VA), 2001 May; Album (4.5 x 6.5) of 4x6 color prints. (Box 28, Folder 398)
    Lady Bird with LSR and Nash and Bette Castro at Williamsburg, Virginia. Album created by Bette Castro.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Wildflower Center, 1995; Color 4x6-5x7 prints. (Box 28, Folder 399)
    Opening of new Wildflower Research Center. Photos of Nash and Bette Castro and family at opening gala; LSR, MFR, Ian and Luci Baines Johnson Turpin. No photos of Lady Bird Johnson.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird: Wildflowers, 1985; Color prints 3.5x5 - 8x10. (Box 28, Folder 400)
    Annotated photos of Lady Bird Johnson and wildflower meadows planted at LBJ ranch and park or along highways. Annotations by Lady Bird Johnson. Photos probably enclosed in Lady Bird to LSR and MFR, December 13, 1985 (in file).
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1964-1971; Black and white and color 8x10 prints. (Box 28, Folder 401)
    LBJ meeting with group concerning California Redwoods (including conservation leaders and Interior Department officials; LSR not present), June 25, 1964 (photo no. 5242); LBJ with LSR and 3 others announcing White House Conference on Natural Beauty, March 12, 1965 (photos 5238- 5239); LSR receiving boxed pen (?) from LBJ, Highway Beautification Act, October 22, 1965 (photos 5240-5241); LSR with LBJ boarding helicopter, MFR, Lady Bird Johnson, and others at Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, June 11, 1971 (photos 5225-5226).
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1968 March 29; OVERSIZED 9.5 x 13/14" black and white prints (2) in 12.5 x 16.5 mat (Box O 65)
    LBJ and Hubert Humphrey receiving guests including LSR and MFR. Two prints: LBJ shaking hands with MFR; LBJ shaking hands with LSR, and autographed card "With best wishes Lyndon B. Johnson" inset in mat. Both prints removed from frames.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1968 July 31; OVERSIZED Black and white, 11x14 print. Photo border inadvertently damaged in removal from frame (bottom edge stuck to glass). (Box O 65)
    Citizens' Advisory Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty. LSR shaking hands with LBJ in front of framed display of signing pens. Photo by Michael A. Geissinger, The White House. Removed from frame.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1968 December 5; OVERSIZED Black and white 7.25x9.25 and 10 x 14 prints in 11.5 x 15.5 mats (Box O 65)
    Two images: LBJ in receiving line shaking hands with LSR, MFR looking on, LBJ speaking to unidentified man on his right; LBJ greeting LSR and MFR (shaking hands). Formal attire. Both photos removed from frames.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1969 January 13; OVERSIZED 11 x 14 prints and 9x12 color photo in 13 x 16 mat. (Box O 65)
    LSR, MFR, Brooke Astor, and other guests at formal dinner at the Plaza Hotel (NY) in honor of LBJ and Lady Bird. Two images with autographed inscriptions to LSR and MFR. 7 prints, including duplicates. Matted image removed from frame.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Library and School of Public Affairs, 1971 May 22; OVERSIZED color 9x11.5 print in 14.5 x 13 mat. (Box O 65)
    Dedication of the Lyndon Baines Johnson Library and Lyndon Baines Johnson School of Public Affairs, The University of Texas at Austin, May 22, 1971. Image of the LBJ Library and grounds, inscribed: For Mary and Laurance, who helped so much to make this possible, Lady Bird and Lyndon B. Johnson. Removed from frame. File includes Dedication program booklet which had been taped to back of frame.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Library and School of Public Affairs, 1971 December; OVERSIZED Color 7.5 x 10 print on 11x14 board (Box O 65)
    Image of LBJ and Lady Bird Johnson in front of the LBJ Library. Inscribed: For Laurance and Mary, with our love and appreciation, Lady Bird and Lyndon Baines Johnson. Photo by Frank Wolfe.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Portraits, 1972 September 18; OVERSIZED Color 6.5x9.5 prints mounted on 11x14 mats. (Box O 65)
    Two informal portraits of LBJ. One inscribed: To Mary and Laurance with affectionate regards, LBJ. Photos by Frank Wolfe. Photos marked Drawer 10.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Portraits, 1974; OVERSIZED 11x14 print in a 13.5x15.5 linen mat. (Box O 65)
    Numbered print (11/300) of portrait of LBJ by Elizabeth Shoumatoff. Not a photograph. Removed from frame.
  - Juliana, Queen of the Netherlands, 1940; 2 black and white 8x10 prints (Box 28, Folder 402)
    LSR escorting Queen Juliana on her visit to Rockefeller Center and Radio City Music Hall. Photo no. 5736. Includes 1992 LSR letter to George LeMoine. See also Autographed Photo Collection file.
  - Kahn, Otto, Undated; Black and white 8x10 print. (Box 28, Folder 403)
    Image obtained from the Metropolitan Opera Association in 1991.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1962-1963; Black and white 3x5-8x10 prints; 1 color 5x7. (Box 28, Folder 404)
    Receiving ORRRC report from LSR in Oval Office ceremony, January 31, 1962; includes MFR and others (photos nos. 5247-5249). Signing ceremony for Outdoor Recreation Act, May 28, 1963, including LSR (photo from Large Album 300-3). One candid shot of JFK and LSR, 1963? (photo no. 5246).
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1984; Black and white 8x10 print (2) and copy negative (Box 28, Folder 405)
    LSR and Kissinger at luncheon for the New York College of Osteopathic Medicine.
  - Kleppe, Thomas S., Undated; Color 4.5 x 6.5 image mounted on 8x10 board. (Box 28, Folder 406)
    Image of Kleppe and LSR. Inscribed: "Laurance - It is a thrill to work with you - Tom Kleppe." Photo removed from frame.
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello, 1946; Black and white 8x10 print (Box 28, Folder 407)
    Autographed portrait of LaGuardia inscribed: "To My Landlord John D. Rockefeller, Jr. from F. LaGuardia, 1946."
  - Leahy, Patrick, 1999; Color 4x6 snapshot. (Box 28, Folder 408)
    Senator Leahy with LSR and Lucy Waletzky at Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park. Includes covering note.
  - Lindbergh, Charles A., 1929-1974; Black and white and color prints, 3x5 - 9x12; negatives. (Box 29, Folder 409)
    Negative of portrait of young Lindbergh, 1929; LSR and unidentified man with Lindbergh, circa 1971 (photo no. 5133, and negatives); Lindbergh with Richard Nixon, Frank Borman, and LSR (Citizens' Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality), on ferry in San Francisco Bay, September 5, 1972; LSR, Donald H. Rumsfeld, and Lindbergh near Golden Gate Bridge, 1972?; 1974 National Geographic clipping showing Lindbergh with LSR and MFR in Hawaii. File includes correspondence with Rumsfeld, and resume for Henry Diamond, 1995.
  - Luce, Clare Booth, Undated; Black and white 8x10 print (Box 29, Folder 410)
    Clare Booth Luce, Brooke Astor, and unidentified man at formal event.
  - McClory, Robert, 1974; OVERSIZED 8x10 black and white, in 10.5 x 12.5 mat. (Box O 65)
    McClory (representative from Illinois), LSR, and MFR. Inscribed: With all good wishes to my friend & star witness Laurance Rockefeller and Mary - Bob McClory, Member of Congress. (Pertaining to NAR Vice Presidential Confirmation hearings) Removed from frame.
  - Margrethe II, Queen of Denmark, and Henrik, Prince Consort, Undated; Black and white 7 x 10 print in 9.75 x 12.5 frame. (Box 29, Folder 411)
    Autographed formal portrait of the royal couple, in leather frame bearing their dual monogram.
  - Maze, Margaret, 1989; Color 3.5 x5 photos. Two photos stuck together; ink marks on others. (Box 29, Folder 412)
    Margaret Maze; Etienne Maze home at Burie (interior); Fred Hechinger; Marie-Louise and Frederick (Maze). Photos by G.(Grace) Hechinger. Also photo of Mill House at St. Georges Hotel, stuck to another photo.
  - Maze, Paul, 1917-1984; Black and white and color 5x7-8x10 prints; one 3x5 print of framed portrait. (Box 29, Folder 413)
    Informal portraits; photos used as illustrations in Anne Singer, Paul Maze, The Lost Impressionist; photos of paintings "Soldiers on Parade" and 1957 painting of horse race event. Note in file: photos and negatives from Fred Weidener. Cross references to photos 200,163 - 200,165.
  - Maze, Paul and Jessie, 1976; Color 8x10 prints (3) on foam board. (Box 29, Folder 414)
    Paul Maze painting and Paul and Jessie Maze at Haye House. Marked Drawer 11 (Friends).
  - Maze, Paul and Jessie, 1976; Color 8x8 and 8x10 prints on foam board. (Box 29, Folder 415)
    Three photos of Jessie Maze and of Paul Maze with Matthew and Jessica Case.
  - Maze, Paul and Jessie, Undated; Black and white and color 3.5 x 5 prints. (Box 29, Folder 416)
    Paul Maze painting and on steps with children and dogs; Jessie Maze standing in field. Three images.
  - Maze, Paul and Jessie, Undated; OVERSIZED 11 x 14 color print on foam board. (Box O 65)
    Enlarged interior shot of Paul and Jessie Maze. Marked Drawer 11 (Friends).
  - Murray, Albert K., late 1940s-1950s, 1995-1996; Color 4x6 prints in album pages. One 5x7 black and white print. (Box 29, Folder 417)
    Album of photos from opening of Christie's retrospective Albert Murray exhibit, December 19-21, 1995. Includes LSR and MFR (and their portraits). Album dismantled in processing. Candid portrait of Murray at table at 834 Fifth Ave.
  - Nicklaus, Jack, Undated; Black and white 8x10 print. (Box 29, Folder 418)
    LSR with Jack Nicklaus and two unidentified golfers at unidentified tournament. Photo removed from frame.
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1960-1972; Black and white 8x10 prints; one negative. (Box 29, Folder 419)
    LSR and NAR with Richard and Pat Nixon at Rockefeller Center campaign rally, October 5, 1960 (photos nos. 5251-5260). Nixon with Charles Lindbergh, Frank Borman, and LSR (Citizens Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality), on ferry in San Francisco, September 5, 1972 (photo removed from frame).
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1971 February 10; Black and white 9 x 13.25 print. (Box 29, Folder 420)
    Nixon receiving LSR at White House with National Industrial Pollution Control Council, February 10, 1971.
  - Pataki, George, 1998, Undated; 2 prints - black and white and color - 8x10. (Box 29, Folder 421)
    Pataki addressing dinner audience, including LSR, DR, Happy Rockefeller; with LSR, DR, and Bernadette Castro at Rockwood Hall ceremony, 1998.
  - Petrie, Milton, Undated; OVERSIZED Color 11x14 printed photo. (Box O 65)
    Autographed printed portrait of Petrie surrounded by stuffed animals. Captioned, Love and Kisses, Milton.
  - Reagan, Ronald and Nancy, 1986-1989, undated; Color 4x6- 8x10 prints; one negative. (Box 29, Folder 422)
    At Kykuit, July 1986, with LSR and DR (laughing),and with LSR, DR, MFR; LSR with Reagan and National Park Service Director William P. Mott, April 28, 1988 (inscribed to LSR and signed by Reagan); LSR at White House with Nancy Reagan and unidentified man, October 4, 1988; LSR and MFR with Nancy Reagan at Rockefeller Center, circa January 1989; Reagan with Millicent Fenwick and with unidentified woman.
  - Reagan, Ronald and Nancy, 1988 April 28; Color 8x10 prints (Box 29, Folder 423)
    Two inscribed photos of Reagans receiving LSR and MFR at White House, signed by Ronald and Nancy Reagan. Photos removed from a double frame.
  - Republican Party, 1980-1996 and undated; OVERSIZED color printed photos, many mounted on mats, 10.5 x 13 - 14 x 18. (Box O 66)
    Printed photos, most with printed inscriptions to LSR or especially to MFR, sent on the part of the Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, the Republican National Committee, Presidential Roundtable, and other groups. Photos of the Senate Majority Leadership; group photos of Presidents Reagan, Nixon, Ford, and George H. W. Bush (and individual photos of Reagan and Bush); Reagan with Margaret Thatcher; Bob Dole. Also includes certificates, printed drawings, and solicitation materials. Four photos removed from frames. Some signatures appear to be originals (Bob Dole, John Heinz).
  - Rhoads, Cornelius P. (Dusty), Undated; Black and white 8x10 print (Box 30, Folder 424)
    Portrait (at MSKCC). Photo no. 5129
  - Rodriguez, Chi Chi, 1991-1995; Color prints, 3- 9x12 and 2 8x10 (Box 30, Folder 425)
    On golf course with LSR, and LSR, MFR with Rodriguez family, December 1991; Rose Bowl grand marshall, 1995. Two photos autographed to LSR and MFR.
  - Roosevelt, Archibald, 1965; Color 3x5 print. (Box 30, Folder 426)
    LSR at formal dinner (Carnegie Museum event) with Archibald B. Roosevelt and member of Mellon family, October 27, 1965. Includes copy of cover letter from Roosevelt, December 15, 1965.
  - Schmidt, Benno C., 1980s-1990s?; Color 4x6 print (Box 30, Folder 427)
    LSR and MFR with Benno Schmidt standing in front of an abstract painting (Kline?). Covering letter in file.
  - Selassie, Haile, 1954 June; Black and white 8x1o glossy prints. (Box 30, Folder 428)
    Visit of Haile Selassie to NBC Studios and Rockefeller Center, June 2, 1954. Includes LSR, JDR 3, Gus Eyssell; Prince Sahle Selassie and Princess Sebla Desta, son and granddaughter of the emperor. Photos include PR captions. Includes photos nos. 5135-5137.
  - Simpson, Alan, 1980s-1990s; Color 4x6 prints (Box 30, Folder 429)
    LSR and MFR with Alan Simpson, senator from Wyoming, and others.
  - Sinatra, Frank, 1981-1982; Black and white and color 8x10 prints; one 3x5 print. (Box 30, Folder 430)
    LSR with Sinatra at benefits for MSKCC (photos nos. 5138-5143). Includes MFR, Barbara Sinatra, unidentified woman. One small print of LSR and Sinatra by Remington sculpture, "Coming through the Rye."
  - Smith, M. Frederik, 1986, undated; Color 4x5 print; black and white 8x10 print (Box 30, Folder 431)
    Fred Smith (with balloons) in his office at Room 5600 (print dated October 1986); speaking at unidentified event.
  - Soldwedel, Frederic, and Clark Gable, 1951; Black and white 8x10 print. (Box 30, Folder 432)
    Soldwedel and Gable on golf course. Photo inscribed: "To Mary and Larry from the Two Kings, 1951 Nassau B., Frederic Soldwedel, Clarke Gable." Photo by Stanley Toogood, Nassau, Bahamas.
  - Stewart, James, 1990; Black and white 8x10 and 5x7 prints. (Box 30, Folder 433)
    Includes photos by Larry French of Jimmy Stewart, LSR, and MFR at Princeton event (tiger, class of 1932); and other photos of unidentified occasion. File also includes Larry French photos of Governor James Florio, and of unidentified man. Letter from Lawrence French to LSR, March 7, 1990, included in file.
  - Strong, Maurice, 1990s?; Color 4x6 print. (Box 30, Folder 434)
    One undated photo of LSR, David Rockefeller, and Maurice Strong standing before portrait of JDR Sr.
  - Talbott, Harold, 1953-1955; OVERSIZED Black and white 9.5 x 10.25 print in 13.75 x 14.5 mat. (Box O 65)
    Harold Talbott, secretary of the Air Force. Inscribed: To Laurance Rockefeller a distinguished American - With my warm regards, Harold Talbott. Photo glued to cardboard backing and mat. Photo removed from frame; some cracking.
  - Teagle, Rhoda Walker French, Undated; Color 5x7 print. (Box 30, Folder 435)
    portrait photo
  - Thatcher, Margaret, 1992; Color 8x10 glossy prints. (Box 30, Folder 436)
    Luncheon with Margaret Thatcher, given by Robert Wood Johnson IV? Includes photo of LSR and Thatcher, inscribed "To Mr. Laurence Rockefeller - all good wishes - Margaret Thatcher." Also includes photo of LSR playing with golden retriever.
  - Victor, Warren and Carol, 2002; Color 4x6 snapshots. (Box 30, Folder 437)
    LSR and Lucy Waletzky, with Carol and Warren Victor and dogs. At Kent House and Playhouse.
  - Wallace, Lila Acheson and Dewitt, Undated; Black and white 3x5 print. (Box 30, Folder 438)
    Informal portrait outdoors. Copy of print from album.
  - Wirth, Conrad L. and Helen, Undated; Color 3.5 x 5 photo in 5x7 mat. (Box 30, Folder 439)
    Mr. and Mrs. Wirth in formal dress. File includes biographical sketch prepared by Ruth Haupert. Removed from frame.
  - Yao Yilin, 1985-1986; Black and white 5x8 - 8x10 prints. (Box 30, Folder 440)
    LSR and MFR (as part of Foreign Policy Association delegation) meeting with Yao Yilin, vice premier of China, in October 1985 (photos nos. 5654-5655); and LSR with Yao Yilin and others at Foreign Policy Association luncheon, New York, 1986? (photos nos. 5669-5671).
  - Zilkha, Cecile (Mrs. Ezra), Undated; Two color snapshots, 4x6 and 5x7. (Box 30, Folder 441)
    LSR and MFR with Cecile Zilkha and unidentified woman, at wedding party for Zilkhas' daughter.
  - Unidentified, 1956; OVERSIZED black and white print in portfolio cover. (Box O 65)
    Portrait by Albert K. Murray done in 1956 of unidentified woman in academic robes, possibly Connie M. Guion? Photograph by Peter A. Juley.
- Religion and Spirituality, 1988-1997, undated; 7
  - Religion and Spirituality: General, Undated; Color 4x6 prints. (Box 30, Folder 442)
    Three unidentified images of sweat lodge frame and blankets.
  - Green Gulch Farm, Undated; Color 8x10 photos. (Box 30, Folder 443)
    Three photos of tea ceremony in meditation hall at Green Gulch Farm (San Francisco Zen Center).
  - HealthCare Chaplaincy, 1997; Black and white 5x7 prints (2). (Box 30, Folder 444)
    LSR at dinner with Father Walter J. Smith, December 1997.
  - A New American Place, 1988, 1990; Color 3.5 x 5 and 4x6 prints. (Box 30, Folder 445)
    LSR, MFR, Marion Weber, at gathering with Sidney Lanier, Thomas Berry, Rollo May, and Naomi Remin, 1988 November 6; Wisdom of Elders awards, 1990 May 12.
- Resorts, 1952-1989; 8
  - Resorts: General, 1960s; OVERSIZED black-and-white and color 11x14 prints mounted on 16x20 mat boards. (Box O 67)
    Portfolio of resorts photos: Caneel Bay, Dorado Beach Hotel, Virgin Gorda (Spring Bay and Little Dix Bay), Mauna Kea Beach Hotel (construction); plus Grand Teton National Park (Colter Bay and Jackson Lake Lodge). Photos mounted on individual mat boards. Portfolio case discarded. Portfolio marked: "Property of Rock Resorts." 19 photos; most are labeled on the back (a few photos appear to have been added to the set).
  - Resorts: General (Clippings), 1966-1967; OVERSIZED album 17 x 14.25 x 1.5. Clippings generally detached from the pages. Handle with care, but can be used without damage. (Box O 68)
    Album of clippings, mainly from magazine articles mentioning Caneel Bay, Dorado Beach, Little Dix, Mauna Kea, and Fountain Valley, Davis Bay.
  - Resorts: General (Unidentified), 1960-1975; Color prints, 2x3 - 8x10; one black-and-white print. (Box 30, Folder 446)
    Unidentified views of bays, port, rainbow. Virgin Islands images, 1975. Aerial views of unidentified beachfront resort development (red roofs). Model (drawing) of unidentified resort development.
  - Resorts: General (Unidentified - Hawaii?), 1978; Color 5x7 prints. (Box 30, Folder 447)
    Unidentified views of golf course, buildings under construction, condos on beach. Prints dated 1978.
  - Resorts: General (Caribbean), circa 1957; OVERSIZED color print (10 x 12.75) and 8.75 x 12.5 print (Box O 69)
    LSR, MFR, NAR, and two women sitting on stone steps, in Caribbean. Photo numbered 5475 (2 copies).
  - Resorts: General (Caribbean), 1978-1979; Color slides (110). (Box 30, Folder 448)
    Dorado Beach Hotel, Cerromar Beach Hotel, and St. Croix. Numbered series of slides, with several gaps. Slides removed from Carousel slide tray.
  - Resorts: General (Caribbean), 1978; Color slides (89) (Box 30, Folder 449)
    St. Croix, Fountain Valley, Davis Bay, Sugar Ruins, Dorado. Includes images of flowers, golfing. Photographed by David Davis. Numbered series of slides, with some gaps. Slides removed from Carousel slide tray.
  - Resorts: General (Caribbean), Undated; Color prints, 8 x 10.75; removed from plastic binder album. (Box 30, Folder 450)
    Underwater photos of coral reef and fish. Photos removed from plastic portfolio album. No identification. (Album was filed in box with Dorado photos.)
  - Caneel Bay: General, early - mid 1950s; Color 5x7 prints, many mounted in paper portfolio frames. One 2.25 x 2.25 color transparency; one color slide. (Box 31, Folder 451)
    Local employees (maids going to work, girl riding on donkey above Caneel Bay, girl holding up basket of fruit; also fisherman with LSR and unidentified associate); LSR with Bancel LaFarge; scenic views. Photos nos. 5455-5462.
  - Caneel Bay: General, mid-1950s-1963; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 31, Folder 452)
    Group photo of LSR and (National Parks Advisory Board), undated; LSR conferring with architects; views of buildings (Sugar Mill restaurant, Hawksnest Bay units, cottage no. 7, Activities Pavilion, rooms); beach views; LSR and MFR posing for photo; LSR and MFR with NAR and Happy Rockefeller; photo of unidentified people by drydocked sailboat ("Radiant") (see also oversized print of this image). Photos nos. 5463-5489.
  - Caneel Bay: General, 1950s-1970s; Color postcards mounted on 8.5 x 11 binder pages; loose 8x10 black and white prints. (Box 31, Folder 453)
    Pages removed from binder album. Portfolio of postcards; inserted photos of resort views, Cinnamon Bay camping, St. John (including photos by Fritz Henle). (Album also contained similar photos of Little Dix Bay, and Grand Teton Lodge Company images.)
  - Caneel Bay: General, 1950s-1970s; Black and white 8x10 prints; 5 color 8x10 prints, 1 negative, 4 color 3x5 prints. (Box 31, Folder 454)
    Publicity photos of bays, beaches, recreation and resort facilities. Includes views of dock, boats, cabin no. 7?, Sugar Mill restaurant, and island views. Also later color photos of restaurants, beach, guest room. Underwater sign and images of parrotfish. Snapshots of "Caneel Bay Momma" boat and crew.
  - Caneel Bay: Early Views and Construction, 1955 and earlier; Black and white 5x7 prints; some larger photostats. (Box 31, Folder 455)
    Views of grounds, clearings, construction materials and sites, bulldozer, donkeys, sugar works. Some photostatic copies (location of originals unknown).